JASON M. GOODE

123 Boerum Pl., Brooklyn, NY 11201 | 973-464-9853 | jmg627@gmail.com | jasonmgoode.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Technology professional with 8+ years of experience spanning engineering and business roles. Most recently, I built software for autonomous vehicles, and graduated from the University of Chicago with an M.S. in Computer Science. Prior to graduate school, I held technology-focused strategy consulting and economic development positions. I'm seeking opportunities where I can use my skills to solve challenging technical problems that address critical customer needs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CARMERA | Google-backed startup building HD mapping software for autonomous vehicles

Software Engineer

Ju

Brooklyn, NY Jun 2019 – Apr 2020

- Built a cloud-based data processing pipeline using Python and AWS to translate map data from source layers to customer format. Reduced processing time by 20% and integrated UI into company's internal web dashboard
- Upgraded map translation and validation software to support next generation of internal road model specification
- Designed an application to analyze raw road scans for critical errors, including LiDAR data, trajectory information, and spherical imagery, saving manual review time and delivering prompt feedback to 3rd party scanning partners
- Developed a map linter for a major German automaker to ensure the integrity of translated data prior to final delivery

Software Engineer – Graduate Intern

Jun - Sep 2018

• Developed internal software tool to automate quality checks on digitized source vectors; wrote geospatial assertions for potential vehicle maneuvers to ensure path-planning reliability (Python, Postgres, Celery, Redis, AWS)

NEW YORK CITY ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION | Grow NYC's tech industry New York, NY Senior Project Manager, Urban Technology & Innovation Jul 2016 – Jun 2017

Project Manager, Urban Technology & Innovation

Jan 2015 – Jun 2016

- Urbantech NYC: Managed a \$7.2M investment in two technology incubators. Program unlocked 130,000 SF of space, programming, and equipment for 50+ NYC tech companies that have collectively raised over \$200M in VC funding
- NYCx: Designed and implemented technology demonstration program that allows companies to pilot new tech on public infrastructure; launched 4 challenges on EV charging, waste reduction, broadband access, and public safety
- Managed two Project Managers and MBA Summer Intern in support of project portfolio

ACCENTURE | Global management consulting firm serving Fortune 500 clients

Strategy Consultant

New York, NY

Sep 2013 – Jan 2015 Sep 2011 – Aug 2013

Business Analyst

- Fortune 500 Utility: Built financial model and supported vendor selection process for a \$500M capital investment in modernizing the utility's statewide metering technology to improve reliability and reduce operating costs by 20%
- <u>Multinational Brewery</u>: Developed strategic plan to improve efficiency of global transportation and logistics operations; identified several technology and operational improvements (e.g. routing, telematics), saving ~\$25M/yr.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO

Chicago, IL

Master of Science, Computer Science

Jun 2017 - Dec 2018

- Graduate Teaching Assistant, Booth School of Business, Entrepreneurship: Urban Opportunities & Solutions
- Projects: NYC Traffic Fatality Predictive Model, Cloud-Hosted Genomic Annotation Service

BOSTON COLLEGE

Bachelor of Arts, Economics

Chestnut Hill, MA Sep 2007 - May 2011

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Skills & Tools: Object-Oriented Programming (Python, Java) | Databases (Postgres, MySQL, Redis, Dynamo) | Cloud Computing (AWS) | Web technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript/React) | UX/UI (Sketch) | Product Management (Jira/Confluence) | Data Analysis (Python, R) | Financial Analysis (Excel) | Presentations (PowerPoint)
- Personal Interests: Cycling, basketball, homebrewing, cooking, technology